<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/it/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>it-it</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/it/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Riccardo Brigatti</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/it/team/riccardo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/it/team/riccardo/</guid>
      <description>Certified ethical hacker and Software engineer graduated from SUPSI. He has accumulated 6 years of experience in the offensive security sector as a penetration tester and Red Teamer for private companies, working from SMEs to the offensive security team of Novartis.&#xA;His advancement in the Swiss army as a non-commissioned officer in the Cyber battalion has improved his technical skills, working with critical infrastructures, and team management. Since January 2024, he has been part of the RED42 sub-detachment, which handles critical offensive operations and advanced training.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matteo Denicolo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/it/team/matteo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/it/team/matteo/</guid>
      <description>Matteo Denicolo has successfully raised over 5 million euros by launching three startups and winning an accelerator. His strategic acumen has led to the increase in value of two companies by 2.5x and 6.5x respectively.&#xA;With 3 years of experience as an executive board member across Switzerland, Italy, and the US, Matteo has demonstrated remarkable leadership and growth capabilities. He doubled the number of employees for a company and tripled its client base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alessio Branca</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/it/team/alessio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/it/team/alessio/</guid>
      <description>Alessio Branca is a seasoned entrepreneur and investor with extensive experience in the healthcare sector, particularly in operations related to the Swiss territory.&#xA;At the age of 21, Alessio spearheaded a startup in the Medical Devices sector, scaling it from 0 to 3 million in revenue within 2.5 years by efficiently managing operations and structuring the entire Swiss market.&#xA;He has founded and structured two companies in the Health Care sector, achieving a remarkable growth trajectory from 0 to 2 million in revenue in just 2 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marco Pagani</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/it/team/marco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/it/team/marco/</guid>
      <description>This young entrepreneur is currently graduating with a B.A. in Science of Economics, majoring in Finance. With a keen interest in the internet business, he is actively developing his own enterprise in this dynamic field.&#xA;His passion for cybersecurity has led him to study IT and digital solutions during his free time. Recently, he showcased his skills by building an entire internet infrastructure, handling everything from hardware setup to device connectivity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diego Omini</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/it/team/diego/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/it/team/diego/</guid>
      <description>Diego Omini is a DevOps engineer and software developer from Switzerland, who has been passionate about programming since 2010. He earned a bachelor’s degree in computer science from the BFH of Bienne. Since February 2023, he has been employed at Swisscom AG as a DevOps engineer.&#xA;Diego specializes in developing RESTful backends using Spring Boot and Java, implementing CI/CD pipelines with Jenkins and GitLab, and deploying applications on Kubernetes. His previous experience includes developing a VR application for his bachelor thesis, automating PST mail archive migrations, and managing a network of 800 workstations and servers during his apprenticeship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/it/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/it/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to TeamFence </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTEM su Red Teaming</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/it/posts/ctem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 17:04:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/it/posts/ctem/</guid>
      <description>Introduzione In TeamFence cerchiamo sempre nuovi modi per migliorare la postura di sicurezza dei nostri clienti. In questo post del blog, discuteremo del framework di Gestione Continua dell&amp;rsquo;Esposizione alle Minacce (CTEM) e di come possa aiutare le organizzazioni a minimizzare l&amp;rsquo;esposizione agli attacchi informatici. Confronteremo anche il CTEM con il Red Teaming e gli attacchi simulati per comprendere i vantaggi di adottare un approccio proattivo alla sicurezza.&#xA;Cos&amp;rsquo;è CTEM? La Gestione Continua dell&amp;rsquo;Esposizione alle Minacce (CTEM) è un framework dinamico e continuo in cinque fasi progettato per minimizzare l&amp;rsquo;esposizione agli attacchi informatici.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rilevamento di HTML Smuggling</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/it/posts/html-smuggling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:04:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/it/posts/html-smuggling/</guid>
      <description>Introduzione L&amp;rsquo;HTML smuggling è una tecnica avanzata e furtiva che sfrutta le funzionalità standard di HTML5 e JavaScript per evitare il rilevamento e distribuire Remote Access Trojans (RAT), malware bancari e altri software dannosi. Questo metodo viene sempre più adottato da gruppi di hacker sponsorizzati dallo stato e criminali informatici per infiltrarsi in governi, individui e aziende. Un esempio notevole è il gruppo NOBELIUM, ritenuto legato alla Russia, che ha utilizzato l&amp;rsquo;HTML smuggling per colpire organizzazioni governative e diplomatiche in tutto il mondo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annunci dannosi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/it/posts/google-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 17:04:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/it/posts/google-ads/</guid>
      <description>Introduzione Nel mondo digitale di oggi, è estremamente facile trovare informazioni online. Spesso utilizziamo motori di ricerca come Google, Bing o DuckDuckGo per aiutarci a trovare ciò che stiamo cercando. Che si tratti di visitare un sito web noto o di scoprire qualcosa di nuovo, i motori di ricerca giocano un ruolo fondamentale nel nostro utilizzo di internet.&#xA;Ma cosa succede quando ci fidiamo troppo di questi motori di ricerca? Immagina di digitare il nome di una famosa azienda su Google e di cliccare su un link che sembra legittimo, ma che in realtà è una truffa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lsass Extractor</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/it/posts/lsass-extractor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 16:39:49 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/it/posts/lsass-extractor/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In TeamFence, we strongly believe that nowadays it&amp;rsquo;s increasingly important for an offensive operator to understand the details behind the techniques and tools.&#xA;For this reason, in this blog post, we will delve into how Mimikatz extracts credentials from lsass dumps, enabling us to then re-implement the logic into a tool tailored to our future needs.&#xA;Note: all the analyses conducted throughout this project have been made on a Windows 11 Enterprise Evaluation workstation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awareness</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/it/services/awareness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 17:04:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/it/services/awareness/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTEM Security</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/it/services/ctemsecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 17:04:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/it/services/ctemsecurity/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Security</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/it/services/websecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 17:04:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/it/services/websecurity/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dettagli CTEM</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ctem-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ctem-details/</guid>
      <description>Introduzione Nel panorama in continua evoluzione della cybersecurity, le organizzazioni sono costantemente alla ricerca delle migliori strategie per proteggere i propri beni digitali. Due approcci prominenti sono il Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM) e il Penetration Testing. Sebbene entrambi mirino a migliorare la sicurezza, lo fanno in modi distinti.&#xA;Cos&amp;rsquo;è il Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM)? Il Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM) è un framework proattivo e adattivo progettato per gestire e ridurre continuamente la superficie di attacco di un&amp;rsquo;organizzazione.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
