<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 17:04:31 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Riccardo Brigatti</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/team/riccardo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/team/riccardo/</guid>
      <description>Certified ethical hacker and Software engineer graduated from SUPSI. He has accumulated 6 years of experience in the offensive security sector as a penetration tester and Red Teamer for private companies, working from SMEs to the offensive security team of Novartis.&#xA;His advancement in the Swiss army as a non-commissioned officer in the Cyber battalion has improved his technical skills, working with critical infrastructures, and team management. Since January 2024, he has been part of the RED42 sub-detachment, which handles critical offensive operations and advanced training.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matteo Denicolo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/team/matteo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/team/matteo/</guid>
      <description>Matteo Denicolo has successfully raised over 5 million euros by launching three startups and winning an accelerator. His strategic acumen has led to the increase in value of two companies by 2.5x and 6.5x respectively.&#xA;With 3 years of experience as an executive board member across Switzerland, Italy, and the US, Matteo has demonstrated remarkable leadership and growth capabilities. He doubled the number of employees for a company and tripled its client base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alessio Branca</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/team/alessio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/team/alessio/</guid>
      <description>Alessio Branca is a seasoned entrepreneur and investor with extensive experience in the healthcare sector, particularly in operations related to the Swiss territory.&#xA;At the age of 21, Alessio spearheaded a startup in the Medical Devices sector, scaling it from 0 to 3 million in revenue within 2.5 years by efficiently managing operations and structuring the entire Swiss market.&#xA;He has founded and structured two companies in the Health Care sector, achieving a remarkable growth trajectory from 0 to 2 million in revenue in just 2 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marco Pagani</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/team/marco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/team/marco/</guid>
      <description>This young entrepreneur is currently graduating with a B.A. in Science of Economics, majoring in Finance. With a keen interest in the internet business, he is actively developing his own enterprise in this dynamic field.&#xA;His passion for cybersecurity has led him to study IT and digital solutions during his free time. Recently, he showcased his skills by building an entire internet infrastructure, handling everything from hardware setup to device connectivity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diego Omini</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/team/diego/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/team/diego/</guid>
      <description>Diego Omini is a DevOps engineer and software developer from Switzerland, who has been passionate about programming since 2010. He earned a bachelor’s degree in computer science from the BFH of Bienne. Since February 2023, he has been employed at Swisscom AG as a DevOps engineer.&#xA;Diego specializes in developing RESTful backends using Spring Boot and Java, implementing CI/CD pipelines with Jenkins and GitLab, and deploying applications on Kubernetes. His previous experience includes developing a VR application for his bachelor thesis, automating PST mail archive migrations, and managing a network of 800 workstations and servers during his apprenticeship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTEM over Red Teaming</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ctem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 17:04:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ctem/</guid>
      <description>Introduction At TeamFence we are always looking for new ways to improve the security posture of our clients. In this blog post, we will discuss the Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM) framework and how it can help organizations minimize exposure to cyber attacks. We will also compare CTEM with Red Teaming and simulated attacks to understand the benefits of adopting a proactive approach to security.&#xA;What is CTEM? Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM) is a dynamic and ongoing five-stage framework designed to minimize exposure to cyber attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTML Smuggling Detection</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/html-smuggling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:04:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/html-smuggling/</guid>
      <description>Introduction HTML smuggling is an advanced and stealthy tactic that leverages standard HTML5 and JavaScript features to avoid detection and deliver Remote Access Trojans (RATs), banking malware, and other harmful software. This method is increasingly being adopted by state-sponsored hacking groups and cybercriminals to infiltrate governments, individuals, and businesses. One notable example is the NOBELIUM group, believed to have links to Russia, which has used HTML smuggling to target government and diplomatic organizations worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malicious Ads</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/google-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 17:04:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/google-ads/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s world of computers, it&amp;rsquo;s super easy to find stuff online. We often use search engines like Google, Bing, or DuckDuckGo to help us find what we&amp;rsquo;re looking for. Whether we want to visit a website we know or find something new, search engines are a big part of how we use the internet.&#xA;But what happens when we trust these search engines too much? Picture this: you type the name of a famous company into Google, and you click on a link that looks legit, but it&amp;rsquo;s actually a trick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lsass Extractor</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lsass-extractor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 16:39:49 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lsass-extractor/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In TeamFence, we strongly believe that nowadays it&amp;rsquo;s increasingly important for an offensive operator to understand the details behind the techniques and tools.&#xA;For this reason, in this blog post, we will delve into how Mimikatz extracts credentials from lsass dumps, enabling us to then re-implement the logic into a tool tailored to our future needs.&#xA;Note: all the analyses conducted throughout this project have been made on a Windows 11 Enterprise Evaluation workstation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Our Vision Our vision is to create a world where cybersecurity awareness is a universal standard, empowering individuals and organizations to protect their digital assets with confidence. As technology advances and cyber threats become increasingly sophisticated, we are committed to staying at the forefront of innovation, providing cutting-edge solutions that anticipate and mitigate risks. We aim to foster a proactive approach to cybersecurity, where education and awareness become integral components of our digital lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awareness</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/awareness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/awareness/</guid>
      <description>At TeamFence, our approach to delivering security awareness is rooted in the belief of knowledge sharing and personnel improvement. We understand the importance of equipping individuals with the necessary skills and awareness to contribute effectively to the security of the organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTEM Details</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ctem-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ctem-details/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the ever-evolving landscape of cybersecurity, organizations are constantly seeking the best strategies to protect their digital assets. Two prominent approaches are Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM) and Penetration Testing. While both aim to enhance security, they do so in distinct ways.&#xA;What is Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM)? Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM) is a proactive and adaptive framework designed to continuously manage and reduce an organization&amp;rsquo;s attack surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Security</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/websecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/websecurity/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is CTEM?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/ctemsecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/ctemsecurity/</guid>
      <description>Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM) is a proactive, five-stage framework designed to minimize exposure to cyber attacks. It helps organizations identify and assess vulnerabilities, map potential attack paths, prioritize risks, and track remediation efforts.&#xA;We start by understanding your current security measures and identifying potential vulnerabilities. This approach combines offensive and defensive strategies (Purple teaming), enabling us to identify and mitigate threats more effectively. By integrating our expertise with your team’s insights, we create a comprehensive defense strategy that is both proactive and adaptive.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
